Guide to the Rice Unversity Center for Research in Parallel Computation (CRPC) records, Ken Kennedy, Scientific Director, 1989-1999 UA 125
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Technical Reports and paper materials, 1989-1999
  - CRPC-TR92230: Standards for Message-Passing in a Distributed Memory Environment, David W. Walker, Oak Ridge National Laboratory, ORNL/TM-12147, August 1992 (Box 19, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92231: The ParaScope Parallel Programming Environment, K.D. Cooper, M. W. Hall, R.T. Hood, K. Kennedy, K.S. McKinley, J.M. Mellor-Crummey, L. Torczon, S.K. Warren. Appeared in Proceedings of the IEEE, February 1993, September 1992 (Box 19, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92232: Compile-time Support for Efficient data Race Detection in Shared-Memory Parallel Programs, J. M. Mellor-Crummey, September 1992 (Box 19, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92233: ADIFOR Working Note #2: Using ADIFOR to Computer Dense and Sparse Jacobians, C. Bischof, P. Hovland, ANL/MCS-TM-158, January 1992 (Box 19, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92234: ADIFOR Working Note #3: ADIFOR Exception Handling, C. Bischof, G. Corliss, A. Griewank, ANL/MCS-TM-159, January 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92235: ADIFOR Working Note #4: ADIFOR: Fortran Source Translation for Efficient Derivations, C. Bischof, A. Carle, G. Corliss, A. Griewank, P. Hovland, ANL/MCS-P278-1291, February 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92236: ADIFOR Working Note #5: ADIFOR: Automatic Differentiation in a Source Translator Environment, C. Bischof, A. Carle, G. Corliss, A. Griewank, ANL/MCS-P288-0192, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92237: ADIFOR Working Note #6: Structured Second- and Higher-Order Derivatives through Univariate Taylor Series, C. Bischof, G. Corliss, A. Griewank, ANL/MCS-P296-0392, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92238: ADIFOR Working Note #8: Hybrid Evaluation of Second Derivatives in ADIOR, C. Bischof, G. Corliss, A. Griewank, ANL/MCS-TM-158, May 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR91239: Design and Parallel Implementation of Two Methods for Modeling the Atmospheric Circulation, I-Liang Chern, Ian Foster. Parallel Computational Fluid Dynamics, ed. K.G. Reinsch et. Al., Elsevier Science Publishers B. V., pp. 83-96, 1992, October 1991 (Box 19, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92240: Automatic Differentiation Applied to Unsaturated Flow ADOL-C Case Study, G. Corliss, A. Griewank, T. Robey, S. Wright, ANL/MCS-TM-162, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92241: Productive Parallel Programming: The PCN Approach, I. Foster, R. Olson, S. Tuecke, MSC-P295-0392. Appears in Scientific Programming, 1(1), pp. 51-66, 1992, March 1992 (Box 19, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92243: Overloading Point and Interval Taylor Operations, G. Corliss, 1992. Appears in Automatic Differentiation of Algorithms: Theory, Implementation, and Application, pp. 139-146, A. Griewank, G. Corliss, eds., SIAM Publications (Box 19, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92244: Automatic Differentiation Bibliography, G. Corliss, 1992. Appears in Automatic Differentiation of Algorithms: Theory, Implementation, and Application, pp. 331-353, A. Griewank, G. Corliss, eds., SIAM Publications (Box 19, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92245: A Robust Trust-Region Algorithm with a Non-Monotonic Penalty Parameter Scheme for Constrained Optimization, Mahmoud El-Alem, September 1992 (revised September 1993) (Box 19, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92246: New SIMD Algorithms for Cluster Labeling on Parallel Computers, John Apostolakis, Paul Coddington, Enzo Marinari, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92247: A Global Convergence Theory for General Trust-Region-Based Algorithms for Equality Constrained Optimization, J. E. Dennis, Jr., Mahmoud El-Alem, Maria Cristina Maciel, September 1992 (revised September 1993) (Box 19, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92249: FORTRAN M: A Language for Modular Parallel Programming, Ian Foster, K. Mani Chandy, MCS-P237-0992, October 1992 (Box 19, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR91250: Rationale for Guaranteed ODE Defect Control, Robert Corliss, George F. Corliss, MCS-P273-1191, December 1991 (Box 19, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR91251: On Implicit Taylor Series Methods for Stiff ODEs, Gabriella Kirlinger, George F. Corliss, MCS-P272-1191, December 1991 (Box 19, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92252: Nonlinear Programming and Domain Decomposition for Partial Differential Equations, J. E. Dennis, Jr., R. M. Lewis, September 1992 (Box 19, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92253: Parallel Processing for Computer Vision and Image Understanding, A. Choudhary, S. Ranka. Appears in IEEE Computer, February 1991, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92254: A Test Suite Approach for Fortran 90D Compilers on MIMD Distributed Memory parallel Computers, Min-You Wu, Geoffrey C. Fox, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92255: Communication Overhead on CM-5: An Experimental Performance Evaluation, Ravi Ponnusamy, Alok Choudhary, March 1992 (Box 19, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92256: Implementation and Scalability of Fortran 90D Intrinsic Functions on Distributed Memory Machines, Ishfaq Ahmad, Alok Choudhary, Geoffrey C. Fox, Kanchana Parasuram, Ravi Ponnusamy, Sanjay Ranka, Rajeev Thakur, March 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92257: Scheduling Regular and Irregular Communication Patterns on the CM-5, Ravi Ponnusamy, Rajeev Thakur, Alok Choudhary, Geoffrey C. Fox, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92258: Software Support for Irregular and Loosely Synchronous Problems, Alok Choudhary, Geoffrey Fox, Sanjay Ranka, Seema Hiranandani, Ken Kennedy, Charles Koelbel, Joel Saltz, May 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92259: Parallel Physical Optimization Algorithms for Allocating Data to Multicomputer Nodes, Nashat Mansour, Geoffrey C. Fox, April 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92260: Applications Benchmarking Set for Fontran D and High Performance Fortran, Nashat Mansour, Geoffrey C. Fox, Gregor von Laszewski, Manish Parashar, Tomas Haupt, Kim Mills, Ying-Hua Lu, Neng-Tan Lin, Nang-Kang Yeh, June 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92261: dependence Analysis for Outer-Loop Parallelization of Existing Fortran 77 Programs, Josef Stein, Geoffrey C. Fox, July 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92262: Allocating Data to Multicomputer Nodes by Physical Optimization Algorithms for Loosely Synchronous Computations, Nashat Mansour, Geoffrey C. Fox, April 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92263: A Runtime Data Mapping Scheme for Irregular Problems, R. Ponnusamy, J. Saltz, R. Das, C. Koelbel, A. Choudhary, April 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92264: Which Applications Can Use High Performance Fortran and Fortran D—Industry Standard Data Parallel Languages? A. Choudhary, G. Fox, T. Haupt, S. Ranka, September 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92265: Mapping Realistic Data Sets on Parallel Computers, R. Ponnusamy, N. Mansour, A. Choudhary, G. C. Fox, September 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92266: Parallel Computers and Complex Systems, Geoffrey C. Fox, December 1992 (Box 20, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92267-S: Automatic Differentiation: Overview and Application to Systems of Parameterized Nonlinear Equations, Marcela Rossemblun, October 1992 (Box 20, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92276: Information Hiding in Parallel Programs, I. Foster, MCS-P290-0292, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR91279: Extending the Farkas Lemma Approach to Necessity Conditions to Infinite Programming, R. A. Tapia, M. Trosset, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR91280: Superlinear and Quadratic Convergence of Primal-dual Interior-point Methods for Linear Programming Revisited, Y. Zhang, R. A. Tapia, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR91281: On the Convergence of Interior-point Methods to the Center of the Solution Set in Linear Programming, Y. Zhang, R. A. Tapia, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92282: Hybrid Simulations of the Effects of Interstellar Pick-up Hydrogen on the Solar Wind Termination Shock, P. C. Liewer, B. E. Goldstein, N. Omidi, October 1992 (Box 20, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92283: Scalar Replacement in the Presence of Conditional Control Flow, Steve Carr, Ken Kennedy, November 1992 (Box 20, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR92284: Improving the Ratio of Memory Operations to Floating-Point Operations in Loops, Steve Carr and Ken Kennedy, November 1992 (revised December 1993) (Box 20, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92285: Embedding Data Mappers with Distributed Memory Machine Compilers, Ravi Ponnusamy, Joel Saltz, Raja Das, Charles Koelbel, Alok Choudhary, May 1992 (Box 20, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92286: Execution-driven Simulation of shared Memory Multiprocessors, S. Dwarkadas, J. R. Jump, R. Mukherjee, J. B. Sinclair, SCS Western Multiconference, December 1992 (Box 20, Folder 4, Item 6)
  - CRPC-TR92287-S: Compiler Analysis for Irregular Problems in Fortran D, Reinhard von Hanxleden, Ken Kennedy, Charles Koelbel, Raja Das, Joel Saltz, December 1992 (revised January 1993) (Box 20, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92288: Superlinear Convergence of the Affine Scaling Algorithm, T. Tsuchiya, R. D. C. Monteiro, November 1992 (Box 20, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92289: On Alternative Problem Formulations for Multidisciplinary Design Optimization, Ervin J. Cramer, Paul D. Frank, Gregory R. Shubin, J. E. Dennis, Jr., R. M. Lewis, December 1992 (Box 20, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93291-S: An Optimizing FORTRAN D Compiler for MIMD Distributed-Memory Machines (Ph.D. thesis), Chau-Wen Tseng, January 1993 (Box 20, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR92292: On the Convergence of Mizuno-Todd-Ye Algorithm to the Analytic Center of the Solution Set, Clovis C. Gonzaga, Richard A. Tapia, June 1992 (revised November 1992) (Box 20, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR92293: On the Quadratic Convergence of the Simplified Mizuno-Todd-Ye Algorithm for Linear Programming, Clovis C. Gonzaga, Richard A. Tapia, June 1992 (revised November 1992) (Box 20, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR92294: On the Quadratic Convergence of the Singular Newton's Method (Essay), R. A. Tapia, Y. Zhang, December 1992 (Box 20, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92295: Molecular Dynamics on a Distributed-Memory Multiprocessor, S. L. Lin, J. Mellor-Crummey, B. M. Pettittm G. N. Phillips, Jr., January 1992 (Box 20, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93296: AMR on the CM-2, Marsha J. Berger, Jeff Saltzman, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR93297: Experiences Using the ParaScope Editor: an Interactive Parallel Programming Tool, Mary W. Hall, Timothy J. Harvey, Ken Kennedy, Nathaniel McIntosh, Kathryn S. McKinley, Jeffrey D. Oldham, Michael H. Palenczny, Gerald Roth, February 1993 (Box 20, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93298-S: Automatic Data Layout for Distributed-Memory Machines in the D Programming Environment, Alan Carle, Ken Kennedy, Ulrich Kremer, John Mellor-Crummey, February 1993 (Box 20, Folder 6, Item 6)
  - CRPC-TR93299-S: Automatic Data Layout for Distributed-Memory Machines (thesis proposal), Ulrich Kemer, February 1993 (Box 20, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93300: DRAFT: High Performance Fortran Journal of Development, Chuck Koelbel, March 1993 (Box 20, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR92301: Compiler Support for Machine Independent Parallelization of Irregular Problems (thesis proposal), Reinhard von Hanxleden, November 1992 (Box 20, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR93302-S: Visoelastic Finite Differencing Modeling, J. O. Blanch, J. O. A. Robertson, w. W. Symes, undated (Box 20, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93303: Calculation and Implementation of the Gradient of the DSO Objective Function for the General Acoustic Model, Alan Sei, March 1993 (Box 20, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - CRPC-TR93304: Loop Level Parallelization of a Seismic Inversion Code, Michel Kern, March 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93305: A Family of Numerical Schemes for the Computation of Elastic Waves, Alan Sei, March 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93306-S: Context Optimization for SIMD Execution, Ken Kennedy, Gerald Roth, April 1993 (revised October 1993) (Box 21, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93307: Preliminary Experiences with the Fortran D Compiler, Seema Hiranandani, Ken Kennedy, Chau-Wen Tseng, April 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR93308: Space-time Concurrent Multigrid Waveform Relaxation, Stefan G. Vandewalle, Eric F. Van de Velde, April 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93309: The Influence of Nodal Constriction on Conduction Velocity in Mylineated Nerve Fibers, J. A. Halter, J. W. Clark, Jr., January 1993 (Box 21, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93310: HPFF Meeting Notes for the January 27-28, 1992 Meeting, Charles Koelbel, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93311: HPFF Meeting Notes for the March 9-10 1992 Meeting, Charles Koelbel, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93312: HPFF Meeting Notes for the April 22, 1992 Meeting, Charles Koelbel, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR93313: HPFF Meetings Notes for the June 8-10, 1992 Meeting, Charles Koelbel, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93314: HPFF Meeting Notes for the July 23-24, 1992 Meeting, High Performance Fortran Forum, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 2, Item 6)
  - CRPC-TR93315: HPFF Meeting Notes for the September 10-11, 1992 Meeting, Charles Koelbel, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93316: HPFF Meeting Notes for the December 10-11, 1992 Meeting, Charles Koelbel, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93317: HPFF Meeting Notes for the March 10-12, 1993 Meeting, Charles Koelbel, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93318-S: Multilevel Algorithms for the Nonlinear Equations and Equality Constrained Optimizations, Natalia Alexandrov, Ph.D. thesis, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR93319: Slicing Analysis and Indirect Access to Distributed Arrays, Raja Das, Joel Saltz, Reinhard con Hanxleden, June 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93321-S: Teaching Parallel Programming and Software Engineering Concepts to High School Students, Adam Rifkin, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93322: On the Convergence of Pattern Search Algorithms, Virginia Torczon, June 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93323: Iloc '93, Preston Briggs, Tim Harvey, July 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93325: A Model for Collaborative Learning with Climatological Data using the Virtual Notebook System and MATLAB, Joel Castellanos, Barbara Elmore, Steven Harris, Leslie Miller, July 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR93326: Derivative Convergence for Iterative Equation Solvers, Andreas Griewank, Christian Bischof, George Corliss, Alan Carle, Karen Williamson, July 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93327: PIERS Timings on Various Parallel Supercomputers, Phillip T. Keenan, Jon Flower, August 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4, Item 6)
  - CRPC-TR93328: Improved Parallel I/O via a Two-phase Run-time Access Strategy, Juan Miguel del Rosario, Alok Choudhary, July 1993 (Box 21, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93329: High Performance I/O for Parallel Computers: Problems and Prospects, Juan Miguel del Rosario, Alok Choudhary, July 1993 (Box 21, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93330-S: NP-Completeness of Dynamic Remapping D Newsletter #8, Ulrich Kremer, August 1993 (Box 21, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93331: Alternating-Direction Line-Relaxation Methods on Multicomputers, John Hofhaus, Eric F. Van de Velde, July 1993 (Box 21, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR93332: A Deterministic Notation for Cooperating Processes, K. Mani Chandy, Ian Foster, August 1993 (Box 21, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93333: Eigenvalues of Block Matrices Arising from Problems in Fluid Mechanics, K. A. Cliffe, T. J. Garratt, A. Spence, August 1993 (Box 21, Folder 5, Item 6)
  - CRPC-TR93334: Problem Formulation for Multidisciplinary Optimization, Evin J. Cramer, J. E. Dennis, Jr., Paul D. Frank, Robert Michael Lewis, Gregory R. Shubin, August 1993 (Box 21, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93335-S: Compositional Oil Reservoir Simulation in Fortran D: A Feasibility Study on Intel i860; Ulrich Kremer, Marcelo Rame, September 1993 (revised December 1993) (Box 21, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93336-S: Integrating Task and Data Parallelism; Berna Massingill, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93337-S: A Code Placement Framework and its Application to Communication Generation; Reinhard von Hanxleden, Ken Kennedy, October 1993 (Box 21, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR93338: Advanced Compilation Techniques for Fortran D; Seema Hiranandani, Ken Kennedy, John Mellor-Crummey, Ajay Sethi, October 1993 (Box 21, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93339-S: Handling Irregular Problems with Fortran D—A Preliminary Report, Reinhard von Hanxleden, October 1993 (Box 21, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93341-S: Optimizing Fortran 90D Programs for SIMD Execution, Gerald Roth, April 1993 (Box 21, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93342-S: Parallelization of Linearized Applications in Fortran D, Lorie M. Liebrock, Ken Kennedy, November 1993 (Box 21, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93343: Mathematical Models for the Speedup of Parallel material Dynamics Codes, Darrell Hicks, Ken Kennedy, Lorie Liebrock, November 1993 (Box 21, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR9334: Homogenization of Compositional Flow in Fractured Porous Media, Todd Arbogast and Z. Chen, undated (Box 21, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93346: On the Implementation of Mixed Methods as Nonconforming Methods for Second Order Elliptic Problems, Todd Arbogast and Z. Chen, undated (Box 21, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - CRPC-TR9334: C++ and Fortran Timing Comparisons, Phil Keenan, November 1993 (Box 21, Folder 7, Item 7)
  - CRPC-TR93349-S: Automatic Data Layout using 0-1 Integer Programming, Robert Bixby, Ken Kennedy, Ulrich Kremer, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93353: PIERS Timings on various Parallel Supercomputers, Phillip Keenan, Jon Flower, November 1993 (Box 21, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93354-S: Very Large-scale Linear Programming: A Case Study Exploiting Both Parallelism and Distributed Memory, Anne Kilgore, December 1993 (Box 21, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93355: Programming in Fortran M, Ian Foster, Robert Olson, Steve Tuecke, October 1993 (Box 21, Folder 8, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR93356-S: Parallelism Using Spatial Decomposition for Molecular Dynamics, Terry Clark, Reinhard von Hanxleden, J. Andrews McCammon, L. Ridgeway Scott, November 1993 (Box 21, Folder 8, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93357-S: Scalable I/O for Our-of-Core Structures, Ken Kennedy, Charles Koelbel, Mike Paleczny, November 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93358: Grid-Clustering: A Fast Hierarchical Clustering Method for Very large Data Sets, Erich Schikuta, November 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93359: The DYPAC System: A Dynamic Processor Allocation and Communication System for Distributed Memory Architectures, Erich Schikuta, November 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93360: The Logical Protocol Unit: Towards and Optimal Communication Protocol, Erich Schikuta, November 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR9336: Dynamic Software Matrices, Erich Schikuta, November 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93362: Computing Large Sparse Jacobin Matrices Using Automatic Differentiation, B. Averick, J. More, C. Bischof, A. Carle, A. Griewank, April 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1, Item 6)
  - CRPC-TR93363: Evaluation of Large-Scale Optimization Problems on Vector and Parallel Architectures, Brett Averick and Jorge Moore, August 1993 (Box 22, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93364: Compiler Technology for Machine-Independent Parallel Programming, Ken Kennedy, August 1993 (Box 22, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93365-S: Value-based Distributions in Fortran D—A preliminary Report, Reihard von Hanxleden, Ken Kennedy, and Joel Saltz, December 1993 (Box 22, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93366-S: From Quads to Graphs: An Intermediate Representation's Journey, Cliff Click, October 1993 (Box 22, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR93367: Runtime Support and Compilation Methods for User-Specified Data Distributions, Ravi Ponnusamy, Joel Saltz, Alok Choudhary, Yuan-Shin Hwang, Geoffrey Fox, November 1993 (Box 22, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93368: An Integrated Runtime and Compile-time Approach for Parallelizing Structured and Block Structured Applications, Gagan Agrawal, Alan Sussman, Joel Saltz, October 1993 (Box 22, Folder 2, Item 6)
  - CRPC-TR94370: Typed Fusion with Applications to Parallel and Sequential Code Generation, Ken Kennedy and Kathryn S. McKinley, January 1994 (Box 22, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR94371: A Global Convergence Theory for SLP and SQP Trust-Region Algorithms, M. El Hallabi, January 1994 (Box 22, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR94372: An Inexact Trust-Region Globalization of Newton's Method, M. El Hallabi, January 1994 (Box 22, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR94373: Numerical Experiments with an Overlapping Additive Schwarz Solver for 3-D Parallel Reservoir Simulation, Luca Pavarino and Marcelo Rame, undated (Box 22, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR94376: Logically Rectangular Mixed Methods for Groundwater Flow and Transport on General Geometry, Todd Arbogast, Mary F. Wheeler, and Ivan Yotov, January 1994 (Box 22, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR94377: Efficient Mixed Methods for Groundwater flow on Triangular or Tetrahedral Meshes, Todd Arbogast, Clint N. Dawson, Mary F. Wheeler, January 1994 (Box 22, Folder 3, Item 6)
  - CRPC-TR94378: The D System: Support for Data-Parallel Programming, Vikram Adve, Alan Carle, Elana Granston, Seema Hiranandani, Ken Kennedy, Charles Koelbel, John Mellor-Crummey, Scott Warren, Chau-Wen Tseng, January 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR94379: Dispersion and Cost Analysis of Some Finite Difference Schemes in One-Parameter Acoustic Wave Modeling, William W. Symes and Quang Huy Tran, February 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93380: Dispersion Analysis of Numerical Wave Propagation and its Computational Consequences, Alain Sei and William W. Symes, November 1993 (Box 22, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR94381: Gradient Calculation of the Travel Time Cost Function by Adjoint State Techniques, Alain Sei and W. W. Symes, February 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR93382-S: Evaluations of the 1993 Spend a Summer with a Scientist Program, August 1993 (Box 22, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR93383: Global Error Control for the Continuous Galerkin Finite Element Method for Ordinary Differential Equations, Donald Estep and Donald French, November 1993 (Box 22, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93384: An Analysis of Numerical Approximations of Metastable Solutions of the Bistable Equation, Donald Estep, November 1993 (Box 22, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - CRPC-TR93385: Integrating Functional and Imperative Parallel Programming: CC++ Solutions to Salishan Problems, John Thornley, December 1993 (Box 22, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - CRPC-TR93386: Concurrent Three-Dimensional Fast Fourier Transform Algorithms for Coarse-Grained Distributed Memory Parallel Computers, Edith Huang, Paulett C. Liewer, Viktor K. Decyk, and Robert D. Ferraro, December 1993 (Box 22, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - CRPC-TR94387: GMRES on (Nearly) Singular Systems, Peter Brown and Homer Walker, January 1994. Revised: August 1995 (Box 22, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - CRPC-TR94388-S: Give-N-Take—A Balanced Code Placement Framework, Reinhard von Hanxleden, Ken Kennedy. Appears in Proceedings of the ACM SIGPLAN '94 Conference on Program Language Design and Implementation, Orlando, Florida, June 1994, March 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - CRPC-TR93389: An Implementation of Balancing Domain Decomposition, Fredrick d'Hennezel, March 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6, Item 2)